what's good guys welcome back to another
forget podcast you guys already know i
haven't uploaded a podcast maybe in like
four weeks it's been a month and you
know what i decided to take like a
little break from the podcast because i
realized that the type of quality that
was coming out wasn't the type that i
wanted to and it wasn't the same as when
i started the podcast if you guys
remember i've gotten you know some ogs
in this industry i've gotten one of the
top traders in the industry all around
the literally the states and i have many
other traders that i have to fly out to
you guys know i feel about the swaggy
i've driven like three hours to go do
podcasts for like other entrepreneurs
and then i realized that you know i
hadn't been pushing out the same quality
that i wanted to i was going to do um a
podcast with another very very very
successful trader and as i'm getting
ready to do the podcast i'm like you
know telling him like a date and stuff
i'm like bro i'm like drained i've been
doing this consistently by myself
obviously i've had help you know by some
of my team
for five months i was five months
consistently uploading a podcast every
single friday and on top of that now i
have this psychology series that i've
come out with you guys i'm like you know
what
let's take a little step back so i can
make sure i get the best type of quality
for you guys and that's exactly what i
wanted to do for this video because this
video is going to be very essential and
i wanted to make sure i didn't rush it i
thought it through every single point
that had to be hit got hit that's why
we're back so appreciate you guys make
sure to like comment and subscribe and
let's get ready into this video where
we're going to be talking about
procrastination as a traitor and how
this affects your success i want you
guys to understand that us as humans we
procrastinate a lot we procrastinate on
a daily basis and this affects us not
only in our trading but in our life
right so we procrastinate the little
stuff oh i'll go wash the dishes later
oh i'll go put the clothes in the dirty
laundry later or i'll throw the trash
out when it gets a little more more full
and like all of these stuff is
procrastinating and this is you just
build up of a bunch of little stuff like
these are all little tiny things that if
we just put our phones down for five
seconds we can literally get done in
five ten minutes max all of these things
they're annoying we get it and since
they're not of importance they could
just be thrown to the side and we
procrastinate and we also tend to do
this you know when it comes to anything
that requires getting out of your
comfort zone such as like trading or
being getting involved in any other
business right and i'm telling you right
now if you don't make this your number
one priority it's just not gonna happen
right and like this is also an issue
because we procrastinate because of how
much distractions we have like i want
you guys to go to your phone right now
pause this video do whatever you got to
do go to screen time on your settings
and on your settings see the average
time you spend on your phone a day i can
guarantee you right now you spend
anywhere from four
to eight hours a day on your phone like
do you guys understand what it is to
spend four to eight hours of your time
on your phone whether it's surfing
through instagram or on snapchat or on
youtube like you like this is four to
eight hours of your day like do you know
how much more productive stuff you could
have done throughout your day versus
just being on your phone being
distracted this takes away so much time
from creativity um innovation and just
being productive as a whole and this is
why you might procrastinate because
you're just comfortable you know just
chilling in your couch surfing through
instagram looking through [__] like this
is so bad for you guys just go to your
settings and go check it out and it's
all gonna make sense in just a little
bit and this is gonna be very important
because time is an asset yes as cringe
and as cliche as that might sound time
is an asset time is money however you
wanna look at it and the reasoning
behind this is because as you're
distracted on your phone surfing you
know through the feed doing whatever you
do or on youtube just watching some you
know [__] videos big deal
this is consuming your time but at the
same time you're procrastinating with
the other stuff like oh i'll do the
dishes when i get back from work or i'll
do whatever when i get back from work
and what this is doing it's creating
this build up inside of your head which
is going and creating a build up in the
back of your head where you're like
alright when i get home from work then
now i can't go studying the charts
because i haven't washed the dishes i
haven't put the clothes away and i
haven't whatever put gas in the car
whatever something else that consumes
the majority of your time and this is
all because of your first
procrastination now you can't get to
learn how to trade or you can't watch
that educational video you can't study
the charts you can't back test you can't
actually deposit money do whatever when
it comes into trading or whatever you
want to do because now you're using that
as an excuse because damn like i have so
much other [__] to do because now you
just procrastinated to do it the first
thing in the morning getting out of the
way then you were distracted the
majority of the day on your phone eating
[__] and then when it just time to get
home later at night and actually put in
the work now you use that as an excuse
like them i have to do all of these
things and you know because i haven't
gotten it there's just so much going on
it's just this build up of all these
little things that is the bigger problem
of why you're not successful it's
because you haven't gotten the little
[__] out of the way so now you can't
focus on your actual craft we could also
procrastinate a lot because we're like
in our comfort zone right this also
falls in line with what i was saying a
little bit earlier i kind of gave like a
little bit of a hint when you're like on
your couch or surfing through instagram
or let's say you actually said you know
what i'm not going to go on instagram
i'm going to go watch this course or i'm
going to go learn this video or i'm
going to do whatever you want for your
craft for your journey for your business
anything that you want to work for
whether it's trading anything that it is
for you to improve yourself but
we tend to do this where on our couch on
our bed and somewhere where we are aware
of our surroundings and we know we're
comfortable when the video starts
getting boring when a video you get a
little distraction your dog your baby
whatever like whatever scenario is going
on now you're like i'll just finish it
later like i got too much going on right
now this is because you are aware of
your surroundings and you're comfortable
you need to get out of your comfort zone
if you're doing something different for
yourself whether it's learning forex or
building your craft you're already
getting out of your comfort zone as it
is because this is different from what
you normally do do the same thing from
where you are around your surroundings
get somewhere else go to a library go
outside go to a starbucks go somewhere
where you're it's different and it's
just like you're uncomfortable in that
place so it gives you no other option
but to focus on what you're supposed to
be working on and same way how it's like
a snowball effect when you procrastinate
everything for the bad like oh i'll do
it later i'll do it later i'll do it
later once you get in this motion of
working towards yourself and once you
start seeing the results and then you
start like getting you know
motivated because you're seeing
everything work it's the same snowball
effect for that like my friends that
like they're around me um they you know
if they're watching this like they they
sometimes hate me because like i am so
far into that snowball effect like where
like if i'm not doing something i don't
feel good like i i don't feel right if
i'm not working towards something
whether it's for me whether it's
something whether i'm just like i just
can't be sitting down and not doing
anything because i feel like i'm wasting
time and there's just opportunities
going out the window and i wasn't always
like this like where you know where i
was three three and a half years ago i
didn't have the same energy the same
like you know drive but like once i
shifted away from just chilling and not
doing anything to like seeing the
results of what happens when you do put
in the work
like how can you not want to keep going
and that's kind of where you guys want
to be at but without making that first
snowball like yes it sucks putting the
snowball like this and then throwing it
but once you throw it and it might ruin
its break okay you got to get another
one build it and do it again throw it
but once that snowball starts going
there's no stopping it so that's why i
feel like you guys need to originally
get that energy and just create it and
just throw it throw it throw it into
obviously it starts having the snowball
effect and once i'm telling you once
that motion gets going it's extremely
powerful the same way how
procrastinating for not doing things if
you have the ability and the power to do
that for not wanting to do it imagine
once you get emotion to wanting to do
things so i have one of my close friends
also very good business partner of mine
um he asked me like how did you get like
this how are you like this motivated
like this drive like how are you always
wanting to work and i'm like it's very
simple bro like one day i asked myself
life is a movie we're living in a movie
right now and i pretend as if there's
somebody following me 24 7 behind me
with one of those big cameras
whenever i'm not doing anything i don't
want people to click off of my movie or
just go to watch somebody else's movie
like i'm always going to be in constant
motion so you don't get out of the movie
theater and stop watching my movie my
documentary or whatever so if there's
always somebody following you with a
camera
watching what you're doing and filming
every single move you're going to want
to make sure that every single
everything that you do is motivational
and you just get [__] done because the
moment you're not doing anything you
know whoever is watching that movie is
going to no longer watch it they're
going to get up and leave and yes let's
say you come back and then do whatever
do other things that are cool for your
movie now you got to reel them back in
and make it worth their time but if you
just keep that motion going they never
get up so i've been on that motion since
four years ago and i just haven't
stopped and i won't stop i'm just gonna
keep that motion going because it only
doesn't better myself it betters
everybody else around me because i
transfer that energy out to everybody
another reason why a lot of people
procrastinate is because of the haters
the haters they hate is the haters
honestly i don't really have much haters
because i don't really do anything for
them to hate like i'm a very positive
person i give out a lot of good stuff if
you're a hater and you're watching this
thanks you know we love you uh we need
more of you guys because you guys are
the first people clicking the video and
watching it watching all the way to the
end to find something to you know hate
so thanks guys if you guys are here um
haters are a lot of reason why many
people procrastinate and this is why
many people are afraid of failure and a
people's opinion towards them if they do
let me say that again people are afraid
of people's opinion it's just an opinion
for example when i got this diamond on
my head for level up obviously the
company that i have with raro and my
other partner is a funding company when
i got this diamond simply like bro that
[__] looks so ugly and i'm like alright
cool it's on my head it's my diamond i
don't care like who cares it's just an
opinion they don't like it i guarantee
if i click on that person's profile they
probably got a worse haircut than i do
because i get a haircut every friday so
the point is it is just an opinion i can
guarantee you that person is just saying
that out of impulse or just because they
want to say something but i guarantee
you like i said he's a follower he's the
first person watching me seeing every
single move that i do and waiting to
give his opinion so don't let somebody's
opinion
define your future don't procrastinate
on working on a craft or make it known
or let that energy out there just
because you're scared of somebody else's
opinion they don't even understand the
niche you're in they don't understand
the business and industry that you're
working towards and the potential out of
it it's very simple they are uneducated
and not worthy of having any effect
towards your future the same way how
that person that didn't like this
diamond very simple they probably don't
even know what goes on behind the
diamond we're changing people's lives
with level up we're funding people
giving them money to go on and do
whatever they want like we just had a
thirty eight thousand dollar payout yeah
they're like do you understand what that
is like this is motivational if that
person just doesn't like it they don't
understand the meaning behind it and
everything that it takes the same thing
when it comes to working for your craft
you can't be scared of somebody else's
opinion towards the potential of what
you have to come so just to close off
here with the hater just to let you guys
know how much you guys affect somebody
because it really doesn't so let's say
for example right now you have a savings
account with 86
400 seconds and then the bank takes 10
bucks because of you know fees or
whatever they take right let's say they
just take ten dollars or he's going to
be like oh what the [__] you know
whatever throw away the whole 86 000
probably not that's still a lot of other
money that's left in there 10 isn't much
right compared to that amount that you
have so
let's say that somebody comes into your
day and says i don't like your shoes or
whatever we have 86 400 seconds in one
day you're gonna let somebody come in
and say oh i don't like your shoes oh
well whatever i don't like your haircut
you're gonna let that one comment mess
up your whole entire day
probably not it's not a big deal it's
such a small portion of so much other
opportunity and window that you have
throughout your day that you literally
just laugh at it you just say hey thanks
hater we needed you here peace out and
that's it that's how the way i i look at
it it's such a small fraction compared
to the potential and everything else
that you can get out of it that it's
literally not a big deal and when it
comes to procrastinating it is very
simple just cut off all distractions
like there is no other excuse if you
know you can use every single point in
this video which i feel like are
extremely valid but it comes down to one
thing if you procrastinate you're making
excuses there cannot be any excuses and
that's it simple you need to understand
that we all have different goals like
there's some people out there like i've
tried to put people on to making six
seven figures a month and they literally
just don't want to they don't want it
they literally said nah that's just too
much work i'm good where i'm at and we
still chill we still have cool
conversations but everybody wants
different goals there's other people out
there such as the haters that they're
okay with they are they just want to
have an opinion somewhere else
same thing with
traders traders want to better their
life so you have to eliminate all
distractions when it comes to that point
you guys need to keep in mind i cut off
every single distraction that i had i
haven't smoked in
probably like four years four or five
years and i recently is when i started
you know having a little drink here and
there but i didn't drink for like three
years almost when i was in this craft i
have cut off all distractions in order
to focus and work on my craft same thing
comes to the charts a lot of you guys
asked me why are my charts so clean how
they look you know so picture perfect
it's because i eliminated all
distractions there as well and as you
guys can see the results of that like
you guys see how simple it is just by
eliminating distractions how everything
becomes more clear and more effective
moral of the story stop reminiscing keep
in mind 2.5 a week is 10 a month 10 a
month is a hundred twenty percent a year
imagine yourself from where you are at
this point right now
one year from now 120
better that sounds like a good
investment any investment any investor
you tell 120 a year they're like where
am i throwing the money at imagine doing
that to yourself let's say you're at
point a 120
one year later you are now at point b c
d so just consistency is key and stop
procrastinating i'll see you guys on the
next podcast appreciate you guys
watching this video all the way to the
end make sure to like comment and
subscribe and
send it forget